DAVID BUSHARD

Vancouver, Washington, 98661

Phone: 360.909.4102 | Email: DavidBushard@gmail.com LinkedIn: <u>linkedin.com/in/davidbushard</u> | GitHub: <u>github.com/DavidBuoy</u> | Behance: <u>https://www.behance.net/davidbushard</u>

Summary

A Creative with a love for all things Design and Media, also a new Developer with a passion to learn and create full stack web applications. Adept at working independently and collaborating as a team across multiple functions. Communicative and willing to ask questions to better the team. Healthy dose of patience and willing to learn from others.

Technical Skills

Tools: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJs, React, Glthub, Adobe Creative Suite

Databases: MySQL, MongoDb

Projects

LoanShark | https://github.com/DavidBuoy/loanShark

Link to live application: https://loaning-sharks.herokuapp.com/

- My final project for the DU bootcamp. The concept of the application is to track different student loans.
- My responsibility was Front End and Design.
- React, MongoDB, Bootstrap Framework.

ParkBuddy 2.0 | https://github.com/DavidBuoy/Project2

Link to live application: https://park-buddy-2.herokuapp.com/

- An application that allows you to view National Parks in your state.
- My responsibilities was Front End and API Calls and Connections
- Javascript, MySQL, Handlebars, Bulma Framework

Design Portfolio | https://www.behance.net/davidbushard

• This is a few design projects that I have worked on throughout my Design career. Both personal projects and also for clients.

- I created all of these different projects
- Adobe Creative Suite: Mainly Photoshop and Illustrator.

Experience

Freelance Graphic Design Buoy Design LLC

Dec 2018 – Present

Vancouver, WA

I did freelance work for various clients for Websites and Graphic Design. Learning every day how to interact with clients and create the desired final project.

Key Accomplishments:

• Learning how to run a business.

Server and Barback

Feb 2012 - June 2020

Famous Daves

Portland, OR

Worked as a Server and Barback. Learned valuable people skills and built relationships with customers, which lead to repeat clients. Was the lead on many large catering events for corporations and weddings.

Notable:

• Was furloughed dew to COVID-19

Web & Graphic Designer

Sept 2018 - May 2019

Zepplin Media

Vancouver, WA

Branding and creating graphics for local businesses around the Vancouver area. Was a part of a team that managed 60 social media accounts for local businesses across the Pacific Northwest.

Graphic Design

Sept 2017 - Nov 2018

City Bible Church

Portland, OR

Was a part of the creative team that branded and built graphics for corporate service on Sunday mornings. Worked in a team setting to create and maintain content.

Graphic DesignClark College

Sept 2015 – Sept 2017 Vancouver, WA

Worked to create social media assets as well as in house assets for the college. Helped maintain and update website keeping classes and imagery up to date. Worked in a team setting to help plan and create quarterly class booklets.

Education

Boot Camp Certificate: University of Denver, Denver, Colorado

A 6 month intensive program focused on gaining Full Stack Web Development skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, NodeJs, React, SQL Databases, MongoDB, Github, and Computer Science.

Associates in Applied Technology: Clark College, Vancouver, Washington A two year degree that specialized in Graphic and Web Design. With emphasis on Adobe Suite programs.